README.md 11/19/2019

Marco Lackovic



Resume

- Last update 19-Nov-2019
- Download the latest version in PDF

Bio

Computer engineer with 5 years of software development experience in the industry, 7 years in the academia as research fellow and teaching assistant. EESTEC alumni. Born and raised in Italy, relocated to Estonia in March 2015.

Languages

• Italian: native speaker

• English: fluent (C1)

• Estonian: intermediate (B1)

• Croatian: elementary

Work Experience

Full stack developer

- GrabCAD, 2018 → present, 1 year: 3D printing order management
 - Tech stack: node.js npm typescript reactjs semantic-ui graphql apollo typeorm postgresql-10 express git github docker kubernetes markdown
 - Tools: windows visual-studio-code teamcity slack jira
- Helmes, 2016 → 2018, 2 years and 10 months: Mobile phone repair management
 - Tech stack: asp.net-mvc C# angularjs javascript yarn bootstrap rest iis-express sqlserver bitbucket git
 - Tools: windows visual-studio-2015 visual-studio-2017 rider octopus postman slack jira confluence ssms tortoisegit

README.md 11/19/2019

- Helmes, 2015, 10 months: Healthcare
 - Tech stack: webforms C# soap javascript bootstrap telerik sql-server
 - Tools: windows visual-studio-2008 visual-studio-2012 ssms

Research fellow

- UNICAL, 2011 → 2015, 4 years: Distributed Data Mining, Grid Computing
 - Tech stack: java globus-toolkit soap web-services latex
 - Tools: linux eclipse

Teaching assistant

- UNICAL, 2007 → 2015, 8 years: Object Oriented Programming, Multi-Threading Programming
 - Tech stack: java c++
 - Tools: linux eclipse libreoffice

Education

- UNICAL 2011: PhD in Computer Engineering
- UNICAL 2007: Master in Computer Engineering

Links

- Stackoverflow
- LinkedIn
- Google Scholar

GitHub

- Profile
- Contributions